In Altryx, there's a few different ways we're able to determine
在 Altryx 中 有很多方法我们可以用来去确定
how many null values we have within our data set.
在我们的数据集中有多少空值
The way that I chose to go about this and
我选择去解决这个问题的方法是使用
I think them easiest way to do is using a summarized tool.
Summarized（概况）工具 我觉得这个方法最简单
So, let me bring one summarize tools into the canvass.
所以 我们拖拽 Summarized（概况）工具到操作界面
Let me drag that in between my input data tool and my browse tool.
把它拖到 input data（输入数据）工具和 browse（浏览）工具之间
I am then going to highlight all of my different fields,
我接下来会重点强调所有不同的字段
meaning I want to make actions on all of these fields.
这意味着我会对所有字段进行操作
The action I'm going to make is within this add section which is going to be
我要进行的操作是在这个 Add（添加）界面
counting the null values.
选中 Count Null（计数空值）选项
This is then going to output all of those different variables and
然后就会在这里输出所有不同的变量和
renaming the fields a little bit.
稍微对字段进行重命名
Let me kick off this workflow now.
现在我开始这个工作流程
What I'm able to see is that most of my fields have no null values,
我能够看到的是大部分字段没有显示 null 值
as you see zero here.
你能在这里看到显示 0
Yet this number of voicemail messages has a very high value
但是 voicemail messages（语音邮件信息）
of missing records.
的缺失记录的数量值很高
As well, we have some within the total date calls.
同时 我们可以看到 total date calls（日期电话合计）的记录
And we have 95 over here at the total night cost as well.
在这里能看到 total night calls（晚上电话合计）的记录是95
This is in my opinion the easiest way to just get a simple count
在我看来 这是在数据集中得到空值记录
of the number of null records within our data set.
的数量的最简单的方法
There are some other approaches like I mentioned before,
有其他的方法可以解决这个问题 我在之前也提过
a great way to analyze nulls within our data set as a holistic approach
在数据集中分析空值的一个很好的方法是
is looking through a field summary tool which will give us the percentage of
使用 Field Summary（字段概况）工具查找 这可以输出
missing records within this data set.
这个数据集中缺失记录的百分比
This is an approach we might take later to determine
这个方法我们可能会在后面使用 这取决于
how we want to actually deal with this number of missing records.
我们实际希望如何去处理缺失记录的数量